Brought to you by Blu-Flash
The Plant Pen
How pretty! Thanks!
I raised them with all my heart, you know.
Oh my, I never had a slightest idea that you love planting flowers, Suneo-san.
"Those who love flowers have a pure heart".
What a show-off.
Mom?
I love flowers, so I wanna plant some.
Last year, someone planted some morning glory seeds...
...but never even bothered to take proper care of it.
And who that boy might be, I wonder?
So what flower do you want?
All I care is about a flower, any would do.
Very well!
You're gonna pull one out?
It's just a pen, huh?
Oh? Disappointed already?
Didn't you want to show-off to Shizuka-chan?....
Yup.
Then allow me to demonstrate.
First, draw a flower.
Then after coloring it...
Do this...
And here's our seed.
The seed?!
Yeah. Now let's plant it.
Pour plenty of water into the pot...
And then we just wait.
And how long does it take?
Just have some patience.
This is the Plant Pen.
It grows exactly as you painted it,
and the more water you pour in, the bigger it will grow.
Yeah, but this flower looks like children's doodles.
I drew it in a hurry.
Then let's draw one from the encyclopedia.
All right! It's done.
Then roll it into a ball...
Wow, how beautiful!
How did you grew it?
Well, let's just say that I really love flowers.
To be honest, it's actually quite easy to plant such flower.
I'm sure you could make them even prettier than me, Shizuka-chan.
I'm looking forward to it!
What? A Plant Pen?
Sounds fun! Let me try it too!
Sure! Here!
It's ready!
Here goes!
She sure drew a lot of 'em...
I beat Suneo in his own game!
Someone must be talking about me...
Well, it's a given considering that a boy as intelligent, refined...
cultured and polite as me is being praised.
Either way, there's no way that Nobita'd plant flowers at his home.
I'm sure he must have bought them at a flower shop. Now, I'm gonna find out the truth!
Huh?
You drew lot of flowers, Shizuka-chan... How beautiful they all look!
I always wanted to be surrounded by flowers like this, at least once in my life.
All right! I'm gonna draw one too.
Come on!
Let us draw!
Ouch!
That hurts, how dare you, Suneo....!
I'm sorry!
I'll make you pay, goddammit.
Now, this tree looks really strange...
What will this bald tree sprout?
Just wait and see.
Tasty, huh?
All right! I'm gonna draw an amusing tree too...
Let's see...
Need a sheet of paper!
Found one!
Washing Machine
User Manual
Why are you pouring so much water?
It's a surprise, you'll see.
Now gimme that bucket.
And now we wait.
How amazing!
It's our home. Let's go and see!
Yay!
This is my room.
A wooden bed.
But the clothes are all wood... I can't wear them...
The cups and dispenser are all made of wood, too.
Let's have some tea on this wood table.
But tea alone is kinda boring.
I'll bring some sweets from our home. I'll be right back.
I have got them!
In the clothes go.
An earthquake!
Help!
Oh, it's about time to dry the clothes.
I shouldn't have drawn the tree house on the washing machine's user manual page...